highfashionhome.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy

High Fashion Home is commited to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information. We will not knowingly collect information or correspond via email with persons under the age of 13 without their parent’s consent. We will presume all personal information collected from our website is from persons age 13 and over.

**Information Collection and Use**

In subscribing for a newsletter, you agree that High Fashion Home may use the data you entered to inform you by email about the contents and/or products selected by you. You may revoke your consent at any time with the effect for the future, either by written notice or by email us via our [Contact Us](https://www.highfashionhome.com/customer-care.html) form. You may also unsubscribe from any newsletter via the link provided at the end of each newsletter. We transfer your data to our service providers only for data administration and hosting purposes.

High Fashion Home will not collect any personally identifiable information from you except when specifically provided by you. Information will be collected, but not is not limited to the following:

  * Placing an online order or in store
  * Creating an account
  * Sign up for emails or catalogs
  * Email correspondence with High Fashion Home representatives
  * Contact Us, Swatch Requests, and other online forms
  * High Fashion Home Rewards Program
  * Sharing your wishlist
  * Entering a contest or sweepstakes
  * Information referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Return an item or make an exchange.

We do not disclose any personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties. We do reserve the right to provide such information to our employees, contractors, law enforcement, regulatory agencies, and agents to enable us to improve company-related services, features, and custom content along with compliance of all applicable laws. We will use all commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard your information. Any information that you provide to us is done at your own risk as High Fashion Home accepts no responsibility for the unauthorized access of personal information held by High Fashion Home under permissable law. 

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our stores or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others, including providers of third party cookie and other third party browsing and use data. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, and to recognize our customers so that we can communicate with you directly about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data analysis and management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, High Fashion Home will support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale, or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their contact information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone, or other solicitations from High Fashion Home.

**Links To Other Sites and Services**

Our website may contain links to other websites, content, or videos (dembedded or direct links( maintained by third parties ("Linked Sites"). High Fashion Home provides Linked Sites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of these Linked Sites does not imply endorsement by High Fashion Home. High Fashion Home does not control the privacy policies or practices of these websites. You should review those policies before providing any personal information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like most websites, we use "cookies" and "web beacon" technology. Cookies and web beacon tehcnologies are used to collect non-personally indentifable information to provide you with customized content and enable certain features of the Site. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A web beacon is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie. You can instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies, which may interfere with the functionality of the Site.

**Security**

High Fashion Home is committed to providing a secure and safe shopping experience. Our servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) that is tested and verified by GoDaddy Inc. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order checkout forms, you can feel at ease shopping our website with one of the leading companies for certifying that a website is secure and encrypted. Transactions on the site are protected with 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption. You can tell you are using the SSL encryption when a green padlock appears in your browser's url address bar.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact us using any of the information below:

**By phone** : | 

1.888.685.3838 

Mon. thru Sat. 10 a.m. - 7 p.m. CST

Sun. 12 p.m. - 6 p.m. CST  
  
---|---  
**By mail** : | 

High Fashion Home 

3100 Travis Street 

Houston, TX 77006  
  
**By email** : | [Contact Us  
](https://www.highfashionhome.com/customer-care.html)  
  
If our information practices change in the future, we'll post an updated policy on our website. 

Last Updated: July 9, 2018
